Ezvid Wiki Privacy Policy
=========================

Effective date: April 20, 2017

* * *

Thanks for entrusting Ezvid Wiki with your research. Consumers like yourself that use our website are well informed, and know that privacy is a serious responsibility. For this reason, we want you to know exactly how we are handling your information.

We collect only the minimal amount of anonymous information necessary to make our website as useful as possible.

• We don't sell information to third parties

• We only use information as this policy describes

How Ezvid Wiki secures your information
---------------------------------------

All web traffic to the domain wiki.ezvid.com is encrypted with SHA256 encryption and we make every reasonable effort to ensure embedded content on our pages use the same level of encryption to protect our users' information.

How Ezvid Wiki uses your information
------------------------------------

If you choose to use our contact form, you will be asked to enter an email address. We may use that email address to contact you in return. We will not share this email address with any third party, or use it for any other purpose.

Cookies
-------

As part of our commitment to minimal tracking, Ezvid Wiki uses a single local storage cookie to **_reduce_** interaction with Google Analytics.

Google Analytics
----------------

We use Google Analytics as a third party tracking service, but we don’t use it to track you individually. We use Google Analytics to collect information about how our website performs and how our users, in general, navigate through and use Ezvid Wiki. This helps us evaluate our users' use of Ezvid Wiki; compile statistical reports on activity; and improve our content and website performance.

Google Analytics gathers certain simple, non-personally identifying information over time, such as your IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring and exit pages, time stamp, and similar data about your use of Ezvid Wiki.

Ezvid Wiki will not, nor will we allow any third party to, use the Google Analytics tool to track our users individually; collect any User Personal Information other than IP address; or correlate your IP address with your identity. Google provides further information about its own privacy practices and offers a [browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) to opt out of Google Analytics tracking.

Certain pages on our site may set other third party cookies. For example, we may embed content, such as videos, from another site that sets a cookie. While we try to minimize these third party cookies, we can’t always control what cookies this third party content sets.

Tracking
--------

"Do Not Track" is a privacy preference you can set in your browser if you do not want online services to collect and share certain kinds of information about your online activity from third party tracking services. We do not track your online browsing activity on other online services over time and we do not permit third-party services to track your activity on our site beyond our basic Google Analytics tracking, which you may opt out of [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Because we do not share this kind of data with third party services or permit this kind of third party data collection on Ezvid Wiki for any of our users, and we do not track our users on third-party websites ourselves, we do not need to respond differently to an individual browser's Do Not Track setting.

If you are interested in turning on your browser’s privacy and Do Not Track settings, the [Do Not Track](http://donottrack.us/) website has browser-specific instructions.

When Ezvid Wiki discloses your information
------------------------------------------

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. However, this does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or providing service to our customers, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect the rights, property, or safety of ourselves or others.

Third party advertising
-----------------------

Ezvid Wiki uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out [this page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

Changes to our Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy at any time, in which instance such changes will be reflected on this page. It is the responsibility of the site visitor to review the current privacy policy on the date of site engagement.

Contacting Ezvid Wiki
---------------------

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, please [contact us](https://wiki.ezvid.com/contact).

#### Learn

#### Discover

* [Wordblast](https://wordblst.com/?utm_campaign=ezvid-wiki-footer) & [Speedwrite Alternatives](https://wiki.ezvid.com/best_speedwrite_alternatives)

#### Get In Touch

* 1958 N. Gramercy Place  
    Los Angeles, CA 90068

 All Rights Reserved © 2009 - 2024 Ezvid, Inc.
